Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Video Productions, 1980-2014; 131.4 Linear Feet in 110 record cartons, 11 cassette boxes, 10 upright video containers, and 2 LP boxes.; 1000 U-matic; 339 MiniDV; 199 VHS; 108 Hi8; 46 Betacam_SP; 16 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 7 S-VHS; 4 Digital_Betacam; 2 DVCAM; 1 Betacam; 1 audiocassette; 2.06
  - Subseries VII.A: Broadcast Videos, 1981-2011
    - Biorhythms, circa 2002
      Produced with Streetworks
      - Dub master, undated (Box 164, U-matic 276_1773)
      - Compilation with On the Real, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1205)
    - Paper Tiger TV Compilation, 2002 (Box 188, Minidv 276_1932)
    - War and the Economy -- Master, 2002 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0232)
    - Who's Paying the Price?, 2002
      - Master, undated (Box 184, Minidv 276_1309)
      - Dub master, 2002 (Box 162, U-matic 276_1754)
    - Anti-war Pro-peace show, MNN Studio, March 29, 2003 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1184)
    - Camera Control -- Manhattan Neighborhood Network Studio Show, 2003-2007
      - #1, April 4, 2007 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1174)
      - #2, April 4, 2007 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1173)
      - #10, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1204)
      - Camera Control MNN Studio Show, Individual monologues, April 4, 2007 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1188)
      - Panel, April 4, 2007 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1175)
      - MiniDV recording, March 29, 2003 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1196)
    - Homeless in Toronto -- Master, 2003 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0235)
    - Hollywood Victory: Delusions of a Maverick as President, 2003
      - Master, 2003 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0237)
      - Master, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1272)
    - Market This!, 2003 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0230)
    - Re-Station The Union Address -- Master, 2003 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0231)
    - Resisting the Empire -- Master, 2003 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0233)
    - Standing with Palestine: U.S. Activism Against the Occupation, 2003-2004
      - Master, May 5, 2004 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0234)
      - Two Activists and a Flag -- Master, 2003 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1258)
      - Rough cut, undated (Box 184, Minidv 276_1323)
      - Rough cut, 2003 (Box 178, Vhs 276_1929)
      - Dub master, undated (Box 154, U-matic 276_1675)
    - Unconventional TV, August 29 - September 3, 2004
      - Program 1, August 29, 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_0904)
      - Program 2, August 30, 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1169)
      - Program 3, August 31, 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1170)
      - Program 4, September 1, 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1182)
      - Program 5, September 2, 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1183)
      - Program 6, September 3, 2004 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1198)
    - Class Dismissed -- Master made from Mini-DV Master, 2004 (Box 68, U-matic 276_0238)
    - Mandate for Democracy, 2004-2005
      - Master, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1257)
      - Rough final, April 6, 2005 (Box 184, Minidv 276_1295)
      - Part one, Tape one, December 8, 2004 (Box 188, Minidv 276_1936)
      - Part one, Tape two, December 8, 2004 (Box 188, Minidv 276_1937)
    - Military Myths, 2004
      - Master, 2004 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1215)
      - DV master, 2004 (Box 184, Dvcam 276_1328)
      - Spanish draft, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1526)
      - 28 minute version, updated, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1294)
    - National Insecurities / Empire and Oil, circa 2004 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1178)
    - Ondas Indigenas (Indigenous Waves), 2004
      - Dub master, undated (Box 162, U-matic 276_1752)
      - MiniDV recording, 2004 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1283)
    - Smokin' Out the Evil-Doers: Unconventional TV Exposes the RNC, 2004
      - Part one, undated (Box 162, U-matic 276_1755)
      - MiniDV recording, October, 2004 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1238)
    - Sir No Sir, 2006; FA_MSS_276_ER_26
    - Paper Tiger Reads Paper Tiger Television, 2007; cuid4748
      - Master (Box 175, Betacam sp 276_1891)
      - Screening Copy (Box 175, Betacam sp 276_1892)
      - U-matic recording, undated; 1 U-matic (Box 14)
    - Love Show, August 7, 2008
      - Tape one (Box 186, Minidv 276_1513)
      - Tape two (Box 186, Minidv 276_1514)
    - Episode #325 [Home on the Frontline], September 17, 2008 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1190)
    - America's Next Top President, 2008
      - Final, May 2008 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1234)
      - Unedited studio show, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1236)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1235)
    - An Emergent Second Life, 2008
      - BCAT Final, December 8, 2008 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1252)
      - BCAT, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1253)
    - BCAT Series, September, 2008
      - Series #1, MNN, September 3, 2008 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1180)
      - Series #1, MNN, September 3, 2008 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1180)
      - Show #2, September 10, 2008 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1214)
      - Series #2, MNN, September 10, 2008 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1171)
      - Show #3, MNN, 2008 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1202)
      - Show #4, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1211)
      - Show #4, MNN, 2008 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1203)
    - Dropping the Rockefeller Drug Laws, 2008; FA_MSS_276_ER_24
    - Paper Tiger TV Reads Election Night, 2008
      - Tape one (Box 183, Minidv 276_1285)
      - Tape two (Box 183, Minidv 276_1267)
    - Urban Environmentalism: DIY Living Green, circa 2009
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1223)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1224)
    - Basta Ya!, 2010
      - MiniDV recording, 2010 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1274)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1222)
    - Paper Tiger Reads 21st Century Working Woman, circa 2010 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1255)
    - Surveilling Surveillance, 2010 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1226)
    - Little Mermaid Singalong, circa 2011 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1217)
    - AIDS Drugs for Africa -- Act 6, undated (Box 141, U-matic 276_1586)
    - Anti Gulf War Compilation: Reports from the Peace Movement, NYC -- Master, undated (Box 162, U-matic 276_1751)
    - Anti Gulf War Segments -- Master, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1256)
    - Bill Bodde Reads TV / From Tom and Jerry to Network TV, undated (Box 77, U-matic 276_0354)
    - Black Liberation Radio: Low Power Empowerment -- Master, undated (Box 113, U-matic 276_0687)
    - Channels of War -- Dub, undated (Box 181, Minidv 276_1181)
    - Compilation dub, undated (Box 153, U-matic 276_1661)
    - Crime Show, undated (Box 154, U-matic 276_1667)
    - Crown Heights Youth Collective Crime Show -- Edited, undated (Box 143, U-matic 276_0920)
    - Dan Hallin -- Translation Mix, undated (Box 142, U-matic 276_0906)
    - Deathrow Notebook / The Killing State, undated (Box 148, U-matic 276_0996)
    - Defense #335, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1250)
    - Democracy Now! DNC, Los Angeles, undated
      - Part one (Box 157, U-matic 276_1700)
      - Part two (Box 156, U-matic 276_1699)
    - Democracy Now! RNC, Philadelphia, undated
      - Part one (Box 157, U-matic 276_1702)
      - Part two (Box 157, U-matic 276_1701)
    - Double Trouble, undated
      - Part 2: Soap Operas (Box 182, Minidv 276_1237)
      - Part 3: Under Siege (Box 182, Minidv 276_1231)
      - Part 8: Do the Write Thing (Box 182, Minidv 276_1227)
      - Reality Unreeled #334 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1248)
    - Dis-Function: A Case of Healthcare Blues, undated; cuid4737 (Box 172, U-matic 276_1859)
    - Family Feud, undated (Box 168, U-matic 276_0528)
    - Fare Raiser II: The Tax Man Cometh -- Dub master, undated (Box 162, U-matic 276_1753)
    - Flo Kennedy on US Press on South Africa, undated; cuid4687 (Box 15, U-matic cuid4687)
      Duration: 26 Minutes
    - From Death Row: Mumia Abu-Jamal -- Dub, undated (Box 151, U-matic 276_1640)
    - Garden Show -- Studio Shoot, undated
      - U-matic recording (Box 146, U-matic 276_0961)
      - VHS recording (Box 146, Vhs 276_0963)
    - Getting a Grip on Access, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1189)
    - Gimme a Break -- Black Sitcoms, undated (Box 78, U-matic 276_0361)
    - The Good The Bad The Illegal: Tom Brokaw Report, undated
      - U-matic recording (Box 141, U-matic 276_1583)
      - Roll-Ins (Box 142, U-matic 276_1593)
    - Hands Off Cuba -- Tape one, undated (Box 142, U-matic 276_1590)
    - Hands on the Verdict, undated (Box 136, Vhs 276_1326)
    - Herb KO's the Corporate Sponsorship of Sports -- Dub Master, Undated; cuid21460 (Box 168, U-matic 276_1815)
    - Herb Schiller Celebration Compilation, undated
      - Master (Box 113, U-matic 276_0694)
      - Dub master (Box 159, U-matic 276_1725)
    - International Women's Day -- Master dub, undated (Box 142, U-matic 276_0917)
    - Iranians in: Down and Out in Beverly Hills, undated (Box 107, U-matic 276_0599)
    - Kathleen Hulser Debones the Poultry Industry: It Takes a Tough Ad Agency to Make a Tender Chicken / Going for the Green: Bill Weinberg Looks at the Marketing of Earth Day and Environmentalism (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0250)
    - Keyan Tomaselli Talks About Media and Resistance in South Africa, undated; cuid41534 (Box 163, U-matic 276_1766)
    - La Familia Indigena / Indigenas en Resistencia -- Master, undated (Box 148, Vhs 276_0989)
    - LA Rebellion -- Studio master, undated (Box 108, U-matic 276_0593)
    - Love Me, Love My Avatar, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1251)
    - No Nukes Special, undated (Box 142, U-matic 276_1588)
    - On the Real, undated
      - Dub master (Box 161, U-matic 276_1750)
      - MiniDV recording (Box 184, Minidv 276_1308)
    - Oscar Owen's 'School of Hard Knocks', undated (Box 138, U-matic 276_1343)
    - Play for Keeps: The Struggle to Save NYC Community Gardens / Road to Ruin: The Real Dirt on SUV's, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1199)
    - Portland NFLCP Studio Master, undated (Box 142, U-matic 276_1594)
    - Processed World: The Magazine with the Bad Attitude, undated
      - #3 (Box 140, U-matic 276_1370)
      - #4 (Box 140, U-matic 276_1369)
      - #5 (Box 140, U-matic 276_1371)
      - #6 (Box 140, U-matic 276_1376)
      - Dub off edit master (Box 138, U-matic 276_1346)
    - Reality Unreeled, #334, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1233)
    - Remembering the American Farm: Scenes from Howell Farm Living History Museum, undated (Box 83, Vhs 276_0471)
    - Reports from the Peace Movement, an Anti Gulf War Compilation, undated (Box 183, Minidv 276_1270)
    - Rhythm and Rights: Radio Station Lok'shini FM, South Africa, undated
      - Dub tape 1 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0487)
      - Dub tape 2 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0483)
    - Sandinista TV -- Part 2, undated; cuid4683 (Box 171, U-matic 276_1853)
    - Satellite As Witness -- Master, undated; cuid41535 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1269)
      Duration: 31 minutes
    - The Scroll Green Chimney Rough Cut, undated; cuid21478 (Box 176, U-matic 276_1903)
      Original format: 3/4" U-matic, Duration: Unknown
    - Shari Rothfarb, Homeless Women, AIDS, and the Media -- Master, undated (Box 108, U-matic 276_0594)
    - Shelia Smith-Hobson on Grenada -- Dub master from two studio originals, undated (Box 76, U-matic 276_0349)
    - Signal to Noise, undated
      - Master (Box 141, U-matic 276_1585)
      - Dub master (Box 158, U-matic 276_1710)
      - U-matic recording (Box 151, U-matic 276_1642)
    - Tiny Mutants on the Sponsor Corporate Ship, undated (Box 144, Betacam sp 276_0930)
    - Torn Between Colors: Youth and the Media / The Weekly Mail -- Mixed, new dub master, undated (Box 70, Betacam sp 276_0258)
    - TV's Gulf War: Bill Nichols Analyzes TV's Coverage of the Gulf War -- Dub master, undated (Box 164, U-matic 276_1774)
    - Two Party System -- Dub master, undated (Box 81, U-matic 276_0409)
    - Video Art Special, undated; cuid4685
    - Withdraw U.S. Bases! Appeal From Okinawa, undated (Box 84, Vhs 276_0504)
    - Women Are Good News, undated
      - Dub master (Box 153, U-matic 276_1662)
      - U-matic recording (Box 153, U-matic 276_1663)
    - Woman With Black Eye -- Democracy Now! Live Broadcast, undated (Box 84, Vhs 276_0519)
    - World Tribunal on Iraq -- Dub for Paper Tiger, undated (Box 182, Minidv 276_1240)
    - World War III Illustrated, undated
      - Master (Box 156, U-matic 276_1692)
      - Master (Box 156, U-matic 276_1693)
      - MiniDV recording (Box 184, Minidv 276_1310)
    - Youth Series, undated
      - #21B Crack is Back (Box 187, Minidv 276_0907)
      - #24 Interviews at Convergence Center Church (Box 187, Minidv 276_0911)
      - #23 Interviews of DC Residents (Box 187, Minidv 276_0908)
      - #21 Interviews, Mon Youth Meeting (Box 187, Minidv 276_0910)
      - #22 Todd's Group (Box 187, Minidv 276_0909)
    - ZTV: Resistance Through Communication -- Zapatista, undated (Box 84, Vhs 276_0505)
  - Subseries VII.B: Non-Broadcast Videos, 1980-2014
    Subseries VII.B Non-Broadcast Videos (1980-2014) contains unreleased and unfinished production elements and video source material, including graphics, soundtracks, and unedited footage of events and interviews.
    Subseries VII.B Non-Broadcast Videos (1980-2014) is arranged chronologically.
    - Blockade of Naval Reserve Station in Seattle, Palestine Solidarity Committee -- Master dub, July 12, 1980 (Box 135, U-matic 276_1163)
    - Demonstration at Federal Building, Westwood, LA, January 19, 1981 (Box 137, Vhs 276_1786)
    - Interview with Marjorie Hill, Director of Office for Lesbian and Gay Community, March 10, 1981 (Box 180, Hi8 276_1047)
    - Grenada Slides, Michelle Gibbs, Bronx paster-up, Brian Winston News Selects, March 16, 1983 (Box 78, U-matic 276_0369)
    - Jeny Apostle, "Drop out!", March 24, 1983 (Box 130, U-matic 276_0881)
    - "Jaguar" Prof. Parry -- Dub, April 10, 1984 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0781)
    - New look, January 6, 1985 (Box 130, U-matic 276_0879)
    - Jim Chladick interview on Interactive Video, March 23, 1986 (Box 104, U-matic 276_0548)
    - Cam control protest 1, March 18, 1987 (Box 181, Minidv 276_1172)
    - Opening Graphics, "V" Shapes, 1987 (Box 148, U-matic 276_0984)
    - Panama -- Resumen Historico, 1987-1990 (Box 125, Vhs 276_1036)
    - CBS Tries the NY3 -- Source material, March 14-21, 1988
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #1, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0579)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #2, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0587)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #3, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0583)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #4, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0584)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #5, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0586)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #6, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0588)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #7, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0580)
      - Jalil Bottom Interview #8 -- Outside prison, March 14, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0578)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #1, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0585)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #2, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0574)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #3, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0575)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #4, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0576)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #5, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0577)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #6, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0582)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #7, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0589)
      - Herman Bell "Badge" Interview #8, March 21, 1988 (Box 107, U-matic 276_0581)
    - Pittston Strike -- Media Working Group, May, 1989
      - Part one (Box 106, U-matic 276_0564)
      - Part two (Box 106, U-matic 276_0569)
      - Pittston -- Master, undated (Box 159, Betacam sp 276_1730)
    - Footage from Palestine -- West Bank and Gaza, July-September, 1989 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0771)
    - Iran tapes, March 1989
      - Map with "It's 8:30...Do You Know Where Your Brain is?" / Dancing Sequence - new show, March 4, 1989 (Box 74, U-matic 276_0318)
      - Owego; PTTV - Tune in next week & address change; Iran - Poet; Peirnter - Bloshes, March 5, 1989 (Box 74, U-matic 276_0315)
      - Owego - Iran, scroll of PTTV tapes (Box 74, U-matic 276_0316)
    - Keyan Tomaselli, 1989, undated
      - Basic rap -- Master, undated (Box 106, U-matic 276_0568)
        Transfer from Hi8
      - Cartoons and cards -- Master, undated (Box 106, U-matic 276_0566)
      - UDC Valpro #1 -- Master, October 27, 1989 (Box 106, U-matic 276_0565)
    - Black Vets for Social Justice -- Role Playing, Job Mashariki, February 20, 1990 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1063)
    - Interview with Nubar Huvsepian by Yanni Damianos, February 25, 1990 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0767)
    - African Market, March 2, 1990 (Box 180, Hi8 276_1042)
    - Black Male Endangered Species, May 1-7, 1990 (Box 129, Vhs 276_0874)
    - South Africa Mags, August 30, 1990 (Box 106, U-matic 276_0567)
    - Exxon Valdez Demonstration, San Diego, September 12, 1990 (Box 127, U-matic 276_1096)
    - Amherst Survey Interview / Flashback #197 -- Cutting room master, September 28, 1990 (Box 103, U-matic 276_0538)
    - America's Defense Monitor -- Military Families Support Network, Press Conference on Capitol Hill, October 10, 1990 (Box 127, U-matic 276_1088)
    - March Against the Middle East War, Cooper Union, NYC, October 20, 1990
      - U-matic recording (Box 130, U-matic 276_0887)
      - U-matic recording (Box 109, U-matic 276_0620)
    - Columbia University -- Edward Said, Rashid Khalidi, Joe Stork on US intervention in Mid-East, October 22, 1990
      - Dub master (Box 122, U-matic 276_0868)
      - U-matic recording (Box 122, U-matic 276_0867)
    - Voices from the Anti-War Movement, Boston, October - December, 1990 (Box 137, U-matic 276_1791)
      Transfer from Hi8 original
    - Fred Neumann, November 1, 1990 (Box 133, U-matic 276_1132)
    - "Azienda Italia" show sent by Caprio, November 29, 1990 (Box 110, U-matic 276_0625)
    - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, Riverside Church, December 2, 1990
      - Part one (Box 120, U-matic 276_0838)
      - Part two (Box 120, U-matic 276_0839)
    - National Guard Send-off, Leahy Press Conference, December 2, 1990 (Box 104, U-matic 276_0547)
    - Demonstration of WRL: getting into body bags, December 7, 1990 (Box 123, U-matic 276_0871)
    - Peace march, Milwaukee -- Dub from edit master, December 8, 1990 (Box 124, U-matic 276_0745)
    - December 14 Interviews, December 14, 1990
      - #151 - Alexandra Allen, David Morrison (Box 124, Betacam 276_0751)
      - #152 - David Morrison (Box 124, Betacam 276_0750)
      - #153 - Joe Stork (Box 124, Betacam 276_0752)
      - Alexandra Allen, Energy Policy Coordinator, Greenpeace (Box 124, Betacam 276_0749)
      - Joe Stork pt. 3, Paul Zaloom (Box 124, Betacam 276_0747)
    - Public Speakout Woodstock Community Centre, Part two -- Master dub, December 16, 1990 (Box 135, U-matic 276_1156)
    - San Francisco Dem Footage and Interviews, December 23, 1990 (Box 125, Vhs 276_1037)
    - "Conversations" with Dr. Aslam Syed, December 26, 1990 (Box 131, U-matic 276_0892)
    - Laura Flanders Speaks About Women, Media and the Military, December 27, 1990 (Box 133, U-matic 276_1131)
    - Gulf Crisis TV Project -- Source material and media elements, 1990, undated
      - Iraq Cutaways -- Part one, November 12, 1990 (Box 132, U-matic 276_1126)
      - Open animation -- Part one master, November 21, 1990 (Box 129, U-matic 276_1119)
      - Open animation -- Part two master, undated (Box 123, U-matic 276_0737)
      - Beginning animation -- Original, undated (Box 147, U-matic 276_0978)
      - Joe Stork, Middle East Report, Paul Zaloom, December 14, 1990 (Box 124, Betacam 276_0748)
      - Paul Zaloom, December 14, 1990 (Box 124, Betacam 276_0746)
      - Gulf Crisis and FAIR Demonstration, undated (Box 124, Vhs 276_0777)
      - Gulf Music, undated (Box 110, U-matic 276_0627)
      - Gulf Music, undated (Box 109, U-matic 276_0615)
      - Gulf War TV Coverage #7, 1991 (Box 126, Vhs 276_1085)
      - Iraq War #3 (from TV), undated (Box 126, Vhs 276_1086)
      - People of Southwest UA, coal field speakout, undated (Box 125, Vhs 276_1038)
      - Segment for the 90's, undated (Box 125, U-matic 276_1034)
      - Selects, undated (Box 131, U-matic 276_0889)
      - Xav #5 Panama, undated (Box 111, U-matic 276_0658)
      - WNYC news, undated (Box 181, Audiocassette 276_1806)
    - Rock Against War (RAW): War Saint for the Soldiers of Misfortune -- Promotional copy, 1990 (Box 110, U-matic 276_0622)
    - Resistance to War in the Middle East, San Francisco, 1990-1991 (Box 121, Vhs 276_0854)
    - Wall Street Demonstration, 1990-1991 (Box 134, U-matic 276_1138)
    - Conversations with Harold Hudson Channer and guest, H.E. Dr. Ali Treiki, January 3, 1991 (Box 113, Vhs 276_0688)
    - "Countdown in the Gulf: War or Peace?" Teach-In by the National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East -- Tape one, January 13, 1991 (Box 126, U-matic 276_1087)
      Transfer from SVHS
    - CBS, NBC, Niteline, January 15, 1991 (Box 165, Vhs 276_1803)
    - United Nations Demonstration Against Gulf War, January 15-16, 1991
      - Tape one -- Master dub, January 15, 1991 (Box 118, U-matic 276_0811)
      - Tape two, January 15-16, 1991 (Box 165, U-matic 276_1805)
    - Los Angeles Federal Building CD Protest Against the War with Iraq, January 16, 1991 (Box 118, U-matic 276_0808)
    - Street interviews, Times Square and Herland Square, N. Cowie, January 17, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1054)
    - Anti-War Protests -- American Indian Museum, San Francisco, January 19, 1991 (Box 119, Vhs 276_0820)
    - National March on Washington Against War in Mid-East -- Master, January 19, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_1051)
    - Desert Calm / A Call to Peace: Dissent in the Streets, January 19-26, 1991 (Box 126, U-matic 276_1080)
    - Demonstration in Madrid, Spain / Demonstration in Montreal, Canada, January 20, 1991 (Box 109, U-matic 276_0614)
    - Che Che Martinez -- Video Arcades interview with Arab store owners, January 21, 1991 (Box 127, U-matic 276_1095)
    - Michael Ratner, January 23, 1991 (Box 130, U-matic 276_0886)
    - "U.S. Out of the Gulf" Demonstration for Peace, Washington, DC, January 26, 1991
      - Demonstration footage, undated (Box 131, U-matic 276_0888)
      - Interviews, demonstration footage (Box 180, Hi8 276_0770)
      - Monica Cleveland, Boarding buses, Interviews on media activism (Box 118, U-matic 276_0816)
      - Norman Cowie, Interviews on media activism (Box 118, U-matic 276_0815)
      - Warriors for the Rainbow (Box 118, U-matic 276_0809)
      - VHS recording (Box 134, Vhs 276_1147)
      - VHS recording (Box 125, Vhs 276_1040)
    - Demonstration Against Media Representation of the War, January 30, 1991
      - Amy Melnick (Box 119, Vhs 276_0823)
      - Media Rally #1 -- Cara Mertes (Box 180, Hi8 276_1050)
      - Hi8 recording (Box 180, Hi8 276_0761)
      - U-matic recording (Box 131, U-matic 276_0895)
    - Bush's State of the Union Address, Media Demonstration, January, 1991 (Box 134, Vhs 276_1146)
    - Demos Contra la Guerra -- Catherine Saalfield, Cuernavaca, January, 1991 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0792)
    - Refuse and Resist Demo, Dover Air Force Base, February 3, 1991 (Box 103, U-matic 276_0529)
    - Eviction and Demolition, South Bronx, February 5, 1991
      - Maquiladoras and the Defense Industry (Box 105, U-matic 276_0556)
      - Squatters / Eviction, Demolition, Home St., South Bronx (Box 179, Hi8 276_0758)
    - Columbia Teach-in, February 7, 1991
      - Hi8 recording (Box 180, Hi8 276_1048)
        Tape may be damaged according to label
      - Hi8 recording (Box 180, Hi8 276_1052)
    - Demonstration, Providence, Rhode Island -- Raw footage, February 9, 1991 (Box 119, Vhs 276_0821)
    - Hatem Bazian on Mid-East history (part 2), James Garrett, RAW Teach-in, February 10, 1991 (Box 127, U-matic 276_1101)
    - Taipei, main cam, February 11, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0769)